<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>pyongyangracer</identifier>
  <mediatype>software</mediatype>
  <collection>open_source_software</collection>
  <collection>community</collection>
  <description>Pyongyang Racer is a 2012 racing game developed by North Korean developer Nosotek and published by Koryo Tours, who commissioned it to promote their services organizing tours into North Korea. As one of the only video games known to be developed in North Korea, at least to be released internationally, it is a curious oddity and fascinating insight into one of the most isolated countries in the world. It's also a pretty shitty game.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Originally, this game was hosted at &lt;a href="http://pyongyangracer.co" rel="nofollow"&gt;pyongyangracer.co&lt;/a&gt;, however since Flash was EOL'd, the site eventually disappeared and has since been picked up by a... video game conference website? While the main SWF file was archived, the game downloads additional assets from the server that are virtually impossible to find.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;This archive contains all the assets required to play the game including the SWF and server assets. Since the vast majority of modern browsers will no longer play Flash games, and the emulator Ruffle is currently not compatible with this game, I recommend using a pre-EOL version of the &lt;a href="https://archive.org/details/flash32beta" rel="nofollow"&gt;standalone Flash player&lt;/a&gt;, which was Adobe's official desktop application for playing and debugging SWF files.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Have fun, and enjoy North Korea.&lt;/div&gt;</description>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.6.4</scanner>
  <subject>pyongyang racer</subject>
  <subject>north korea</subject>
  <subject>video game</subject>
  <subject>game</subject>
  <title>Pyongyang Racer</title>
  <uploader>itsmattkc@gmail.com</uploader>
  <publicdate>2022-05-18 04:16:41</publicdate>
  <addeddate>2022-05-18 04:16:41</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20220518044430[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
</metadata>
